[{"answer": "You must have a lot of Polish people --", "docId": "120615pmt", "aSentId": 33, "question": "Why are you such a big deal?", "qSentId": 32}, {"answer": "Well, I've been really lucky to be at places where their brand helped me right away.", "docId": "120615pmt", "aSentId": 40, "question": "What does it mean to you to have that reputation?", "qSentId": 39}, {"answer": "I think you learn -- you learn from every experience, but a loss puts you in a position where you're more reflective, you can -- you go to deeper places than you do with a win.", "docId": "120615pmt", "aSentId": 56, "question": "Do you believe as a coach instinctively you can learn more from a loss than a victory?", "qSentId": 55}, {"answer": "Well, the very first thing is you don't go with assumptions.", "docId": "120615pmt", "aSentId": 69, "question": "Why do you think that happened in Athens, and what are you going to do to stop it happening in London when the whole world assumes you're going to win gold quite easily?", "qSentId": 68}, {"answer": "I think about it often, because I --", "docId": "120615pmt", "aSentId": 89, "question": "How often do you think about that game?", "qSentId": 88}, {"answer": "Not hourly.", "docId": "120615pmt", "aSentId": 91, "question": "Hourly?", "qSentId": 90}, {"answer": "Well, the very first thing is you're honest with them.", "docId": "120615pmt", "aSentId": 128, "question": "How do you get it to gel and to work where they have to share that status?", "qSentId": 127}, {"answer": "Well, I don't know.", "docId": "120615pmt", "aSentId": 150, "question": "Why is ego now seen as a stick to beat people with?", "qSentId": 149}, {"answer": "It is.", "docId": "120615pmt", "aSentId": 158, "question": "It's all part of the same thing, isn't it?", "qSentId": 157}, {"answer": "Yes, I don't think it is.", "docId": "120615pmt", "aSentId": 179, "question": "Is the American dream still as attainable as it was when you were young?", "qSentId": 178}, {"answer": "Well, you know, it -- intellect does not know race, color, nationality, gender.", "docId": "120615pmt", "aSentId": 190, "question": "-- then how can we blame them?", "qSentId": 189}, {"answer": "RZYZEWSKI: Well, the main thing is to be truthful, where you're honest with one another.", "docId": "120615pmt", "aSentId": 200, "question": "What are the values that you like to instill in them, human values?", "qSentId": 199}, {"answer": "No, it was horrible, and I've respected Coach Paterno my entire life and had a chance to get to know him really well in the last year of his life.", "docId": "120615pmt", "aSentId": 216, "question": "It was a very sad thing, though, wasn't it?", "qSentId": 215}, {"answer": "Well, you should deal with it like -- like any team should deal with it.", "docId": "120615pmt", "aSentId": 226, "question": "What should Joe Paterno perhaps have done that he didn't?", "qSentId": 225}, {"answer": "Well, incredible commitment.", "docId": "120615pmt", "aSentId": 235, "question": "What does it take to be a champion in sports, and not just a winner, or a good sportsman, or even necessarily a great sportsman, but a champion over a long period of time?", "qSentId": 234}, {"answer": "I'll decide on that after it's over.", "docId": "120615pmt", "aSentId": 246, "question": "What would that mean to you personally?", "qSentId": 245}, {"answer": "Yes, well, you keep it simple.", "docId": "120615pmt", "aSentId": 262, "question": "What do you say to guys like that at that moment?", "qSentId": 261}, {"answer": "Yes, they do.", "docId": "120615pmt", "aSentId": 274, "question": "Do you think those guys in that moment understand that playing for their country beats anything else?", "qSentId": 273}, {"answer": "Eleven.", "docId": "120615pmt", "aSentId": 298, "question": "Do you even know how many you won?", "qSentId": 297}, {"answer": "No, world championship, I know I have in the teens, but I'm not sure where.", "docId": "120615pmt", "aSentId": 301, "question": "In total, in your career and everything?", "qSentId": 300}, {"answer": "Female athlete, American.", "docId": "120615pmt", "aSentId": 311, "question": "Is it just swimmer or athlete in total?", "qSentId": 310}, {"answer": "Oh, that's a really nice way to say that.", "docId": "120615pmt", "aSentId": 320, "question": "Are you the female Michael Phelps or is he the male Natalie Coughlin?", "qSentId": 319}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "120615pmt", "aSentId": 339, "question": "Because when he stands there to dive in, he must want to kill everyone, right?", "qSentId": 338}, {"answer": "We are competitive by nature.", "docId": "120615pmt", "aSentId": 341, "question": "Isn't that what this is all about?", "qSentId": 340}, {"answer": "Just before it starts.", "docId": "120615pmt", "aSentId": 348, "question": "Before the race or during the race?", "qSentId": 347}, {"answer": "I'm incredibly nervous.", "docId": "120615pmt", "aSentId": 355, "question": "Are you nervous?", "qSentId": 354}, {"answer": "The swimmer's nightmare is not getting your suit on.", "docId": "120615pmt", "aSentId": 362, "question": "What is the swimmer's nightmare?", "qSentId": 361}, {"answer": "It's pretty incredible.", "docId": "120615pmt", "aSentId": 368, "question": "What does it take to you to be an American competing in the Olympic games, which is watched by the whole world?", "qSentId": 367}, {"answer": "It's an emotional event.", "docId": "120615pmt", "aSentId": 392, "question": "Why were you so emotional?", "qSentId": 391}, {"answer": "I love the day to day.", "docId": "120615pmt", "aSentId": 412, "question": "Why continue?", "qSentId": 411}, {"answer": "It does.", "docId": "120615pmt", "aSentId": 422, "question": "Being in your late 20s and being called old?", "qSentId": 421}, {"answer": "No, never.", "docId": "120615pmt", "aSentId": 475, "question": "Could you even imagined just how well this has gone?", "qSentId": 474}]